{
"id": "33503fa7",
"metadata": {
"uuid": "33503fa7",
"user_agent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/99.0.4844.82 Safari/537.36",
"meta_created": 1649694674364,
"logs": [
{
"type": "info",
"message": "Audio ended"
}
],
"note_method": "none",
"time_paused": 0,
"times_paused": 0,
"digit_span_time_taken": 42639,
"digit_span_score": 10,
"started_quiz": 1649694878270,
"submitted_quiz": 1649694937293,
"time_taking_quiz": 59023
},
"questions": [
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "How long have Jackson and Davies been friends?",
"correct": "40 Years",
"option1": "10 Years",
"option2": "20 Years",
"option3": "40 Years",
"option4": "5 Years",
"answer": "20 Years"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What state do they live in?",
"correct": "Washington",
"option1": "Indiana",
"option2": "Minnesota",
"option3": "Michigan",
"option4": "Washington",
"answer": "Indiana"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What are their favourite pastimes?",
"correct": "Going for walks and gardening",
"option1": "Playing chess and swimming",
"option2": "Going for walks and gardening",
"option3": "Going to church and birdwatching",
"option4": "Playing bingo and jogging",
"answer": "Going for walks and gardening"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Which does Davies not grow?",
"correct": "Beets",
"option1": "Beets",
"option2": "Peas",
"option3": "Melons",
"option4": "Carrots",
"answer": "Beets"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What do they do with their harvest?",
"correct": "Make jams and preserves",
"option1": "Donate it to chairty",
"option2": "Give it away to friends and family",
"option3": "Make jams and preserves",
"option4": "Make pies and cakes",
"answer": "Make jams and preserves"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What relation do Liam and Robert have to each other?",
"correct": "Cousins",
"option1": "Classmates",
"option2": "Friends",
"option3": "Cousins",
"option4": "Brothers",
"answer": "Cousins"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "How old is Liam?",
"correct": "8 years old",
"option1": "6 years old",
"option2": "5 years old",
"option3": "8 years old",
"option4": "10 years old",
"answer": "10 years old"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Who's car did they go in?",
"correct": "Aunt Sally",
"option1": "Uncle Devin",
"option2": "Aunt Sally",
"option3": "Liam's father",
"option4": "Liam's mother",
"answer": "Aunt Sally"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Where did they go in the car?",
"correct": "Riding school",
"option1": "Cooking school",
"option2": "The mall",
"option3": "Riding school",
"option4": "The playground",
"answer": "Riding school"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "When did their lesson start?",
"correct": "3 o'clock",
"option1": "3 o'clock",
"option2": "2 o'clock",
"option3": "Noon",
"option4": "1 o'clock",
"answer": "1 o'clock"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Who was Lucy Carson visiting?",
"correct": "Her brother",
"option1": "Her mother",
"option2": "Her nephiew",
"option3": "Her sister",
"option4": "Her brother",
"answer": "Her brother"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Which state did she visit?",
"correct": "Virginia",
"option1": "Missouri",
"option2": "Virginia",
"option3": "Connecticut",
"option4": "Louisiana",
"answer": "Louisiana"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Where was she going did when she got lost?",
"correct": "The art musium",
"option1": "The gallary",
"option2": "The library",
"option3": "The art musium",
"option4": "The bookstore",
"answer": "The art musium"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "Where did she leave the directions?",
"correct": "On her dresseer",
"option1": "In her car",
"option2": "In her brothers appartement",
"option3": "On her couch",
"option4": "On her dresseer",
"answer": "In her brothers appartement"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "How many blocks did she have to walk north?",
"correct": "5 blocks",
"option1": "15 blocks",
"option2": "5 blocks",
"option3": "2 Blocks",
"option4": "1 Block",
"answer": "15 blocks"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What day of the week did the annual sale start on?",
"correct": "Tuesday",
"option1": "Friday",
"option2": "Monday",
"option3": "Tuesday",
"option4": "Thursday",
"answer": "Tuesday"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "How much were sporting goods marked down?",
"correct": "75%",
"option1": "25%",
"option2": "75%",
"option3": "50%",
"option4": "15%",
"answer": "25%"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "How many dollars were jackets reduced by?",
"correct": "30$",
"option1": "100$",
"option2": "50$",
"option3": "30$",
"option4": "60$",
"answer": "30$"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What were the crowds of shoppers bumping into?",
"correct": "Each other",
"option1": "The employees",
"option2": "Each other",
"option3": "Carts",
"option4": "Racks of cloths",
"answer": "Each other"
},
{
"type": "multiple_choice",
"question": "What did each employee receive after closing?",
"correct": "A bottle of champaign",
"option1": "A Gift card",
"option2": "A sincere thank you",
"option3": "A bottle of champaign",
"option4": "A bottle of wine",
"answer": "A bottle of wine"
}
]
}